const cquizData = [{
    Question:
        'What is a correct syntax to output "Hello World" in C?',
    Options: [
        'Console.WriteLine("Hello World");      ',
        'cout <<"Hello World";',
        'printf("Hello World"); ',
        'System.out.printline("Hello World");',],
    Correct: 2,
}, {
    Question:
        'How do you insert COMMENTS in C code?',
    Options: [
        '// This is a comment    ',
        '-- This is a comment',
        '# This is a comment',
        '* This is a comment',],
    Correct: 0,
}, {
    Question:
        'When a variable is created in C, a memory address is assigned to the variable.',
    Options: [
        "Don't Know ",
        'True    ',
        'False',
        'None',],
    Correct: 1,
}, {
    Question:
        'In C, code statements must end with a semicolon (;)',
    Options: [
        "Don't Know",
        'False   ',
        'True     ',
        'None',],
    Correct: 2,
}, {
    Question:
        'How can you create a variable with the numeric value 5?',
    Options: [
        'num = 5 int;     ',
        'val num = 5;',
        'num = 5;',
        'int num = 5;  ',],
    Correct: 3,
}, {
    Question:
        'How can you create a variable with the floating number 2.8?',
    Options: [
        'float num = 2.8;      ',
        'num = 2.8 float;',
        'num = 2.8 double;',
        'val num = 2.8;',],
    Correct: 0,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which operator is used to add together two values?',
    Options: [
        'The ADD keyword     ',
        'The + sign    ',
        'The & sign',
        'The * sign',],
    Correct: 1,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which function is often used to output values and print text?',
    Options: [
        'printword()   ',
        'write()',
        'printf() ',
        'output()',],
    Correct: 2,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which format specifier is often used to print integers?',
    Options: [
        '%s    ',
        '%c',
        '%d  ',
        '%f',],
    Correct: 2,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which operator can be used to compare two values?',
    Options: [
        '=     ',
        '==    ',
        '<>',
        '><',],
    Correct: 1,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which operator can be used to find the memory size (in bytes) of a data type or variable?',
    Options: [
        'The sizeof property     ',
        'The sizer property',
        'The len property',
        'The length property',],
    Correct: 0,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which keyword can be used to make a variable unchangeable/read-only?',
    Options: [
        'constant',
        'final',
        'const  ',
        'readonly',],
    Correct: 2,
}, {
    Question:
        'What do we call the following? int myNumbers[] = {25, 50, 75, 100};',
    Options: [
        'A class    ',
        'A pointer',
        'An array   ',
        'None of the above',],
    Correct: 2,
}, {
    Question:
        'Array indexes start with:',
    Options: [
        "Don't know",
        '1  ',
        '0   ',
        'None ',],
    Correct: 2,
}, {
    Question:
        'How do you call a function in C?',
    Options: [
        '(myFunction);   ',
        'myFunction;',
        'myFunction();',
        'myFunction[];',],
    Correct: 2,
}, {
    Question:
        'How do you start writing an if statement in C?',
    Options: [
        'if (x > y)     ',
        'if x > y()',
        'if x > y',
        'if x > y then',],
    Correct: 0,
}, {
    Question:
        'How do you start writing a while loop in C?',
    Options: [
        'while x < y then  ',
        'while (x < y)   ',
        'if x > y while',
        'while x < y',],
    Correct: 1,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which keyword is used to return a value inside a function?',
    Options: [
        'void   ',
        'break',
        'return ',
        'get',],
    Correct: 2,
}, {
    Question:
        'How do you start writing a for loop in C?',
    Options: [
        'for (int i = 0; while < 5; i++)   ',
        'for (int i = 0; switch < 5; i++)',
        'for (int i = 0; i < 5; i++)',
        'for (x in y)',],
    Correct: 2,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which statement can be used to select one of many code blocks to be executed?',
    Options: [
        'break    ',
        'default',
        'when',
        'switch  ',],
    Correct: 3,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which statement is used to stop a loop?',
    Options: [
        'exit  ',
        'stop',
        'break  ',
        'void',],
    Correct: 2,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which keyword is used to create a class in C?',
    Options: [
        'class    ',
        'None of the above',
        'class()',
        'class = myClass',],
    Correct: 1,
}, {
    Question:
        'What is ptr in the following code known as? int* ptr = &myAge;',
    Options: [
        'An array     ',
        'A parameter',
        'A class',
        'A pointer',],
    Correct: 3,
}, {
    Question:
        'In C, it is possible to inherit class properties and functions from one class to another.',
    Options: [
        "Don't Know",
        'True   ',
        'False',
        'None    ',],
    Correct: 2,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which keyword is used to create a structure?',
    Options: [
        'str    ',
        'struct     ',
        'structure',
        'structs',],
    Correct: 1,
}]
